- So you secured the
back and you secured all
the windows?
Great job, guys.
Ms.Sparks, you're
perfectly safe now.
- Actually I feel very safe.
- Why don't I show
you how this works?
Push this button
and you punch in any
number that you feel
comfortable with.
That's it, it's easy.
- Okay , thank you.
Duane?
- Yeah?
- [Ms. Sparks] Can I offer
you something to drink?
("I'll Make Love To
You" by Boyz II Men)
- Listen I really would
love to, but I have some
other jobs to attend to.
Maybe another time?
- Okay
- I do know your code.
Wait, if you ever need
me, I mean for the
system that is,
just give me a call.
- Okay.
- All right?
- Thank you.
- [Duane] Don't forget.
♪ Close your eyes, make a wish ♪
♪ And blow out the candlelight ♪
♪ For tonight is
just your night ♪
♪ We're gonna celebrate, ♪
♪ All through the night ♪
♪ Pour the wine,
light the fire ♪
♪ Girl your wish is my command ♪
♪ I submit to your demands ♪
♪ I will do anything, ♪
♪ Girl you need only ask ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ And I'll hold you tight ♪
♪ Baby all through the night ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ When you want me to ♪
♪ And I will not let go ♪
♪ Till you tell me to ♪
♪ Girl relax, let's go slow ♪
♪ I ain't got nowhere to go ♪
♪ I'm just gonna
concentrate on you ♪
♪ Girl are you ready ♪
♪ It's gonna be a long night ♪
♪ Throw your clothes
on the floor ♪
♪ I'm gonna take my
clothes off too ♪
♪ I made plans to be with you ♪
♪ Girl whatever you ask
me you know I can do ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ And I'll hold you tight ♪
♪ Baby all through the night ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ When you want me to ♪
♪ And I will not let go ♪
♪ Till you tell me to ♪
♪ Baby tonight is your night ♪
♪ And I will do you right ♪
♪ Just make a wish
on your night ♪
♪ Anything that you ask ♪
♪ I will give you the
love of your life ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ And I'll hold you tight ♪
♪ Baby all through the night ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ When you want me to ♪
♪ And I will not let go ♪
♪ Till you tell me to ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ And I'll hold you tight ♪
♪ Baby all through the night ♪
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ When you want me to ♪
♪ And I will not let go ♪
♪ Till you tell me to ♪